珍妮丝有一个问题 你们六人当中有哪一个人
Janice has a question. Who of the six of you...
跟你们当中的另一个人睡过？
... has slept with who of the six of you?
好下流的数学问题
Wow,it's like a dirty math problem.
很抱歉，答案是一个也没有
I'm sorry,the answer there would be none of us.
是的，知道吗，如果那个不马上改变的话
Yeah. You know what?lf that doesn't change soon...
我将为了别人把你给轰出去
...l'm going to dump you for somebody who puts out.
这几年下来 你们都没有喝醉做蠢事？
Over the years,none of you ever got drunk and stupid?
这可完全不是同一个问题
Well,that's really a different question.
想不到一群成天混在一起的人
I can't believe a group of people who spends this much time together...
居然没做过丑事
... has never bumped uglies.
莫妮卡曾经和瑞秋在一起
There was that one time Monica and Rachel got together.
什么？
What?
很抱歉，没有那回事
Excuse me,there was no "time."
那就假设有
Okay,but let's say there was.
会怎么样？
How might that go?
那就告诉我
Well then answer me this:
你们有没有差一点…？
Have any of you ever almost...?
还有谁要咖啡？ 外面有狗狗
-Anybody need more coffee? -Hey,there's a dog out there!
本集播出：“倒叙”
The One With the Flashback
“三年前”
太可惜了？ 怎么了？
-That is so unfortunate. -What?
可爱裸男越来越胖
Cute Naked Guy's starting to put on weight.
我马上回来
I'll be back in just a minute.
菲比，抱歉 我的口红印到电话筒了
I'm sorry that I left lipstick marks on the phone.
你没有啊
You didn't leave lipstick marks on the phone.
那就是你，再见
Then it must have been you. Bye.
再见
Bye-bye.
所以我才要搬走 说到这件事
-That's why I moved out. -Hey,while we're on that...
你几时要告诉我妹妹 你不住这里了？
...when are you gonna tell my sister you don't live here anymore?
在某些层面上，她已经知道了
On some level,she already knows.
她并不知道你每天晚上溜出去
She doesn't know you sneak out every night...
每天早上溜回来
...and back every morning...
而且已在你外婆家住了一星期
...and that you've been at your grandmother's for a week.
好吧，也许不是这些层面
Okay,well,maybe not on those levels.
你必须告诉她
You have got to tell her.
你拖得越久，面对她越困难
The longer you wait,the harder it is going to be on her.
你说得对，你说得对
You're right. You're right.
听着，今晚的包
Anyway, listen, tonight's bag...
太重了，你能否帮我偷偷把东西弄出去
...is really bulky.So could you sneak stuff out for me?
比如像这个定时收音机和一些墓地的泥土
lt's just like a clock radio and some cemetery dirt.
我永远也找不到室友
I'm never gonna find a roommate. Ever.
没有好的人选？
Nobody good?
有个家伙养了一堆雪貂
There was the guy with the ferrets.
是一堆喔
That's plural.
有一个爱吐口水 还有一个觉得我的名字很好玩
The spitter. And the guy who enjoyed my name so much...
每次说到都要发出怪声
... he made a noise every time he said it.
幸会，钱德宾，宾！
"Nice to meet you,Chandler Bing. Bing!"
好棒的房子，钱德宾 宾！
"Great apartment,Chandler Bing. Bing!"
明天还有几个？ 两个
-How many more tomorrow? -Two.
一个好像很无趣的摄影师
This photographer who seemed really dull...
和一个怪怪的演员
...and this actor guy who I'm not sure about.
我拿起电话说“钱德宾”
When I answered the phone "Chandler Bing"...
他居然说：哇，好短的留言
... he said,"Whoa! Short message!"
罗斯，脚放下 否则以后不准来
Foot on the floor or come over no more.
你的梳妆台都不见了 她只注意到这个
Your dresser is missing,but this she notices.
什么？ 我该走了
-What? -I have to go.
卡萝应该回家了，所以…
Carol should be home by now,so....
你们两个还好吗？ 有改善了
-How's it going with you guys? -Better,actually.
我终于知道我们为何有这些困扰
I finally figured out why we're having so much trouble.
真的？ 对，你们也知道我有你们
-Oh,really? -Yeah. You know how I have you guys?
她自己没有要好的朋友
She doesn't have any close friends that are just hers.
不过上星期，她在健身房 认识一个叫苏珊的女人
But last week,she met this woman at the gym,"Susan" something.
她们一拍即合 这样一来就不一样了
And they really hit it off,and I think it's gonna make a difference.
艾瑞克
So,Eric...
你是哪一种摄影师？
...what kind of photography do you do?
大部份是流行时尚
Oh,mostly fashion.
偶尔会有模特儿过来 没关系吧
There may be models here sometimes. I hope that's cool.
没关系
Yes,that is cool.
因为有模特儿来的机率…
Because I have models here,you know...
是零
... never.
这个夏天 我都到我姐的海边小屋度周末
During the summer I spend most weekends at my sister's beach house...
也欢迎你去玩
...which you're welcome to use.
不过我得告诉你 她是色情明星
Although I should tell you,she's a porn star.
我还要见一个人
Well,I still have one more person to meet.
不过除非她是你姐姐…
But unless it turns out to be your sister...
你的机会应该很大
... I think your chances are pretty good.
好
All right.
卧房、浴室、客厅
Bedroom,bathroom,living room.
这里是厨房，谢谢你来 再见
This here is the kitchen,and thanks for coming by. Bye-bye.
你不想问我问题吗？
Don't you wanna ask me any questions?
好…
Sure.
你好吗？
What's up?
我是演员
Well,I'm an actor.
我很爱干净
I'm fairly neat.
我自己有电视
I got my own TV.
你放心，我不排斥同性恋
Oh,and don't worry,I'm totally okay with the gay thing.
什么同性恋？
What gay thing?
就是一般的同性恋的事
Just,you know,in general. The whole "people-being-gay" thing.
我完全不在意
Totally cool with that.
乔利，谢谢你来
Okay,Jerry. Thanks for stopping by.
（上帝啊！）
Oh,my God!
莫妮卡
Hey,Mon.
想听一件很烂的事吗？ 时刻准备着
-Wanna hear something that sucks? -Do I ever!
克里斯要把酒吧关闭 不会吧
-Chris says they're closing the bar. -No way!
这里要改成一家咖啡店
They're turning it into a coffee place.
只卖咖啡？
Just coffee?
我们以后要去哪里？ 我怎么知道
-Where are we gonna hang out? -You got me.
一瓶啤酒 室友挑好了吗？
-Can I get a beer? -Did you pick a roommate?
那当然 是那个意大利帅哥吗？
-You bet. -ls it the ltalian guy?
是的
Yeah,right.
他好可爱
He's so cute.
这就是我需要的，一个我可以跟在他后面的室友
That's what I want. A roommate I can walk around with...
被当成是“一个可笑的人”
...and be referred to as "the funny one."
球台空了，准备一下 我马上回来
Table's free. Rack them up. Back in a minute.
准备让我打屁股吧
Get ready for me to whip your butt.
好，不过之后要打球
Okay,but after that,we're shooting some pool.
不对，很抱歉
Excuse me? Hello? Hi.
我朋友点的是洋葱
My friend ordered an onion...
不是橄榄
... not an olive.
我点的是甜酒和健怡可乐
And I ordered a rum and Diet Coke...
这杯不是
...which I don't think this is.
对不起 没关系
-I am so sorry. -That's all right.
准备饮料能有多难？
How hard is it to get a couple drinks right,huh?
我们来敬酒
I would like to propose a toast...
这位女士在一年后的今天 就要成为…
...to the woman who,in one year from today,will become...
贝瑞巴伯医生、牙科博士夫人了
... Mrs. Dr. Barry Barber,D. D.S.
应该再秀一次戒指了
I think it's time to see the ring again.
很棒吧？ 就好像一辈子都有男朋友
Isn't it exciting? I mean,it's like having a boyfriend for life!
是啊，我知道
Yeah. I know.
怎么了？
What?
我不晓得
Oh,I don't know.
也许只是想到…
Well,maybe it's just the idea...
一辈子要跟贝瑞在一起
...of Barry for the rest of my life.
我不知道，我觉得…
I don't know,I think l....
我想来个最后的放纵
I feel like having one last fling...
就是跳出我自己的系统
...just to sort of get it out of my system.
瑞秋，别说了 你好坏
-Rachel,stop! -You're so bad!
我是认真的 我真的觉得我需要…
I'm serious. I really think I need to just have...
毫无意义的性爱
...some meaningless sex,you know?
就跟下一个看到的男人
With the next guy I see.
抱歉，我的球好像掉了
Excuse me,I seem to have dropped my ball.
所以呢？
Yeah,so?
我又把它捡起来了
And now I've picked it up again.
天哪，那是我的高中同学
My God! I went to high school with her.
-瑞秋，嗨！-莫妮卡
-Rachel，hi！-Monica
她是不是在对我竖中指？
ls she giving me the finger?
莫妮卡！你觉得如何？
Monica！Look! Hi! What do you think?
天哪
Oh,my God!
连泰坦尼克号都撞不坏它
You can't even see where the Titanic hit it.
没错，他叫贝瑞 是一位医生 非常感谢
Yes,his name is Barry. He's a doctor,thank you very much.
这是你一直以来的梦想，恭喜你
Just like you always wanted. Congratulations.
谢谢 那你呢？有对象吗？
Thank you. So how about you? Are you seeing anybody?
目前没有
Not right now.
没关系
Oh,well,that's okay.
我知道
I know.
我要去找我朋友了
So I think I'll get back to my friend.
好…
Oh,yeah. Sure,sure,sure.
下次我进城，我们一起吃饭？
Can we have lunch the next time I'm in the city?
好啊
That'd be great.
再见 再见
-Okay. -Thanks.
我赌十块钱这辈子都不会再见到她
Ten bucks says I never see that woman again in my life.
真的，没关系
No,honey,really. It's fine.
你就…
Just...
跟苏珊去吧
...go with Susan.
真的，我觉得…
Really,I think
我觉得女生一起出门很好啊
I think girls' night out is a great idea.
好…好，再见
Okay. Okay. Bye.
她们要做什么？ 不晓得，女生做的事
-What are they doing? -I don't know. Something girly.
你回来早了
Hey,you're early.
你拿着那盏灯做什么？
What are you doing with the lamp?
拿去换电线
Just taking it to get rewired.
别送去你修音响那一家 他们已经修了一星期
Don't take it where you took the stereo. They've had that over a week.
哈克先生 我们没有制造噪音
Mr. Heckles,no one is making any noise up here.
你们打扰我练习双簧管了
You're disturbing my oboe practice.
你又不会吹双簧管 我可以吹
-You don't play the oboe. -I could play the oboe.
那就请你小声一点
Then I'm gonna have to ask you to keep it down.
你是谁？
Who are you?
艾瑞克，钱德的新室友 我才是钱德的新室友
-I'm Eric,Chandler's new roommate. -I'm Chandler's new roommate.
不是吧 我可以当钱德的新室友
-I don't think so. -I could be Chandler's new roommate.
但是他打电话告诉我… 他是亲口告诉我的
-But he told me over the phone -He told me in person.
好奇怪
That's weird.
我要回我的新公寓了
I'm going to go into my new apartment now.
又见面了
Hi again.
谢谢你
Thank you so much.
别谢我，谢那个没出现的混蛋
Don't thank me. Thank the jerk that never showed up.
我要去上班了
Okay,I gotta get to work.
并不是为了钱，而是因为不时得会有人
And not just for the money.But because every now and then...
走出卫生间时脚底会粘着马桶垫纸
...someone walks out of the bathroom with a little bit of toilet paper on their shoe.
需要帮忙吗？ 不用了，我可以
-You want some help? -No,thanks. I got it.
我不行
No,I don't!
没事吧？
You okay?
我起来得太快了，头有点晕
I stood up too fast. Got a little head rush.
天太热了
It's the heat.
而且又潮湿
And the humidity.
加起来…
That's...
实在蛮难受的
...a tough combination.
想不想进来喝杯柠檬汁？
Do you want to come in for some lemonade?
想得不得了
Like you wouldn't believe.
你家好漂亮
This is a great place.
谢谢
Thank you.
自己随意不要客气
Just make yourself comfortable.
懂了
Gotcha.
这其实是我奶奶的房子
So this place is really my grandmother's.
她搬去佛罗里达，我才能住 否则我根本租不起
I got it when she moved to Florida. Otherwise I could never afford it.
要是房东问起
So if the landlord ever asks...
你就说我是87岁… 害怕录影机的老太太，你渴吗
... I'm an 87-year-old woman who's afraid of her VCR. You thirsty?
渴得不得了
You bet I am!
好
Okay...
这是你的阴茎！
... here's your penis!
天哪！你在干什么？
Oh,my God! What the hell are you doing?
你问我想不想进来喝柠檬汁
You said,"You wanna come in for some lemonade?"
所以呢？
So?
你只是要给我柠檬汁？ 是啊
Were you just gonna give me lemonade?
赶快遮起来！
Cover yourself up!
对喔，抱歉
Oh,right. Sorry.
我真不敢相信
God,I don't believe this!
人家请你喝柠檬汁 就是想跟你上床？
Someone asks you in for lemonade and that means they want to have sex?
通常是啊，不只柠檬汁啦
Usually,yeah. Well,not just lemonade.
冰茶啦，果汁啦
Iced tea,sometimes juice.
我很抱歉，我只是…
Look,sorry. I just
我以为你喜欢我
I thought you liked me.
我真混蛋
I'm such a jerk.
没关系
It's okay.
任何人都会碰上这种事
I suppose it could happen to anyone.
我不认识这种人，不过…
Not anyone I know,but....
我还是看得到
By the way,I can still see it.
菲比，你的床呢？
Where's your bed?
不在屋里吗？
It's not in the apartment?
居然又发生这种事了
I can't believe this is happening again.
什么？ 好，别拷问我了
-What? -Okay,enough with the third degree!
我…我不住这里了
I don't live here anymore.
你在说什么？ 对不起
-What are you talking about? -I'm sorry.
我不住这里了
I don't live here anymore.
我不知道该怎么告诉你 但是其他人都知道
I didn't know how to tell you. But,you know,everybody else knows.
大家都知道？
Everybody knows?
这本来是好事 但是我忘了原因
That was supposed to be a good thing. I forget why.
我不明白，我原以为我们以后会相处很好
l don't understand.l thought we were doing better lately.
是的，只要我搬走就可以
Yeah, 'cause l moved out.
我曾经一整个月睡不着
Do you know I couldn't sleep for a month...
就因为我在沙发垫上 滴了一滴墨水
...because I got a dot of ink on one of the sofa cushions?
你可以把它翻面啊
You could've just turned the cushion over.
我本来会翻，但另一面 沾到意大利面酱汁
I would have,but I had a spaghetti stain on the other side.
什么？
What?
这就是我要说的
This is what I'm talking about.
我要住在可以打翻东西的地方
I need to live in a land where people can spill!
你可以打翻东西啊…
Well,you can spill.
在水槽里
In the sink.
亲爱的，不是你不好 你就是这样
Oh,honey. It's not your fault,you know. This is who you are.
我爱你，我要我们是朋友
And I love you. And I want us to be friends.
要是我留在这里 那是不可能的
And if I stay here,I don't see that happening.
我也爱你 那就好
-I love you too. -Good.
怎么了？
What?
什么？我只是很难过
What? I'm just sad.
才怪，你在想是哪一个垫子
No,you're not. You're wondering which cushion it is.
我为什么不能两个都想？我的意思是，我可以想两件事情
Well, why can't l think of both?l mean, l can think two things.
继续吧，看，你知道你需要什么的，加油
Go ahead. Look.You know you want to. Go.
上帝啊
Oh, my God!
在看什么？
So what are you watching?
“海滩游侠”
Baywatch.
在演什么？
What's it about?
救生员
Lifeguards.
听起来蛮蠢…
Well,it sounds kind of stup
她是谁？
Who's she?
妮可艾格（名模）
Nicole Eggert.
我们喜欢她
We like her.
哇，她们在跑
Wow! Look at them run!
她们经常在跑
They do that a lot.
你要喝啤酒吗？
Hey,you want a beer?
我去拿 别起来，冰桶在这里
-I'll get one. -Don't get up. I got a cooler here.
你有啤酒吗？我们的喝完了
Do you have any beers? We're out of beers.
自己拿
Help yourself.
你还好吗？
You okay?
菲比搬走了
Phoebe moved out.
对
Right.
我不懂
I don't understand.
我真的这么难相处？ 所以才找不到男朋友？
Am I so hard to live with? Is this why I don't have a boyfriend?
不是，你没有男朋友是因为…
You don't have a boyfriend because....
我不知道为什么
I don't know why you don't have a boyfriend.
你应该要有的
You should have a boyfriend.
我也这么认为
I think so.
过来
Come here.
来
听我说 你是我最喜欢的人之一
Listen,you are one of my favorite people...
还是我在现实中所认识 最漂亮的女人
...and the most beautiful woman I've ever known in real life.
人都在哪里？
Where is everybody?
已经关门了，克里斯要我锁门 出了什么事？
It's already closed. Chris gave me the keys to lock up. What is wrong?
我想我的婚姻…
I think my marriage...
应该是完蛋了
...is kind of over.
不会吧，为什么？
Oh,no! Why?
因为卡萝是女同性恋
Because Carol's a lesbian.
而我不是女同性恋
And I'm not one.
而且这显然不是一时激情
And apparently it's not a mix-and-match situation.
天哪
Oh,my God!
我真不敢相信
I don't believe it!
可怜的孩子
Oh,you poor bunny.
我是白痴
I'm an idiot.
我早该看出来了
I mean,I should have seen it.
卡萝和我出门 她都会看漂亮女人
I mean,Carol and I would be out,and she'd see some beautiful woman...
她会说：罗斯，你看她
...and she'd be "Ross! Look at her!"
我还觉得…
And I'd think...
天哪，我老婆真酷
... "God,my wife is cool."
你觉得那个苏珊 是她的情人吗？
Hey,do you think that Susan person is her lover?
我现在知道了
Well,now I do!
对不起
I'm sorry.
都七年了
Seven years!
我们在一起七年了
I mean,we've been together seven years.
她是唯一爱过我的女人
She's the only woman who's ever loved me.
也是我唯一有过…
She's the only woman I've ever....
真好
This is nice.
我知道，很棒对不对？
I know. It is,isn't it?
我是认真的，摸起来好舒服
No,I mean it. This feels really good.
是百分之百纯棉吗？
Is it 100% cotton?
对，而且还是特价品
And I got it on sale too.
我的意思是，看起来疙疙瘩瘩的，但不是
l mean, it looks nubby, but...But it's not.
我该走了
I should go.
有一个救生员正要拆除核弹
One of the lifeguards was just about to dismantle a nuclear device.
我们待会可以去喝一杯
If you want to get a drink later,we can.
听起来不错
That sounds great.
哦，听着，事情一定会…
Oh,and listen,it's gonna be
我知道
I know.
谢了
Thanks.
搞不好可以避免 要是我再有深度一点
Maybe this wouldn't have happened if I'd been more nurturing...
或是多注意她一点
...or I'd paid more attention...
或是我有子宫
...or I had a uterus.
我真不敢相信 我知道
-I can't believe it. -I know.
你不该受这种折磨，真的
You know,you don't deserve this. You don't,Ross.
你人这么好 谢谢
-You're so good. -Thanks.
而且你很体帖
And you're so sweet.
谢谢 心肠又好
-Thanks. -And you're kind.
谢谢
Thanks.
过来
Come here.
等一下
Wait,wait,wait.
别管了
It's okay.
等一下，我的脚卡在球洞里
Wait,wait,wait! My foot is stuck in the pocket.
什么？ 我弄不出来
-What? -I can't get it out.
女生可不想听到这种话
That's not something a girl wants to hear.
你别逗我
Come on,don't start.
怎么了？
What?
那些烂球好碍事
Stupid balls are in the way.
好吧
Oh,well.
这不是最有建设性的解决方式
That probably wouldn't have been the most constructive solution.
你的脸上有粉笔灰
You have chalk on your face.
罗斯，你说得对 我怎么会一直以为这是真的草皮
You're right. I don't know why I always thought this was real grass.
你还好吗？
Honey,you okay?
我老婆是同性恋
My wife's a lesbian.
酷！
Cool!
罗斯，乔伊，乔伊，罗斯
Ross,Joey. Joey,Ross.
不敢相信你竟然回来了
I can't believe you came back.
什么都不要说
Don't say anything.
我不想说话，我不想思考
I don't wanna speak. I don't wanna think.
我只要你现在就抱起我吻我…
I just want you to take me and kiss me and make love to me right here...
跟我作爱
... right now.
瑞秋……
Rachel…
-什么？-你错过出口了
-What? -You missed the exit.
对不起
Sorry.
上帝啊，你在想什么？
My God,what were you thinking about?
贝瑞
Barry.